https://www.expensepoint.com/globalpoint-and-your-privacy/

Skip to contentAbout UsGDPRSSAE18 – SOC I Type IIContactBecome a ResellerPrivacy & SecurityTerms of UseAt GlobalPoint we respect your right to privacy and we understand that, as a visitor to expensepoint.com or globalpointtech.com we may ask you to register or to provide personal information and preferences when you visit certain areas of expensepoint.com, globalpointtech.com, download free software, or request information.We will guard the personal information you share with us to ensure the content, services, and advertising that we provide on expensepoint.com are always tailored to your current, designated preferences.When you provide GlobalPoint with your name (or alias), e-mail address, mailing address, or telephone number, GlobalPoint and GlobalPoint representatives and affiliates may use the provided information to alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information, classes, new services, and other GlobalPoint information, or sales contacts. Representatives and affiliates may include value-added resellers and authorized training partners. Beyond its representatives and affiliates, GlobalPoint does not offer or allow the selling of any user-provided information to third parties.GlobalPoint respects the rights users give us when opting to receive e-mail communications and enforces internal policies to preserve those rights. It is our objective to retain the long-term ability to continue to communicate with our users.If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still visit most GlobalPoint websites; however, you will not have access to areas that require personal identification.Personal information that you post to online forums is accessible by other forum participants.If a user elects to use our “Tell A Friend” application for forwarding a GlobalPoint e-mail to their friend or informing a friend about our website, we ask them for the friend’s name and e-mail address. GlobalPoint will automatically send the friend the specified e-mail or the specified website information. GlobalPoint will not use the friend’s information to contact them in the future.ExpensePoint.com membership and the use of log files (cookies)GlobalPoint also utilizes visitor log files (cookies) and hosted tracking with our website. Once a user enters our site, a cookie follows them through their click stream path. Examples of information being collected by these cookies and the hosted tracking include the number of times a user came to our site(s), and the paths they took to get there. GlobalPoint uses the data collected from website visitor cookies and hosted tracking in aggregate form only and does not collect any personally identifiable information. Use of this information helps us better understand what users are seeking and learning at our website(s) and helps us identify potential navigation issues.How GlobalPoint will protect your personal informationGlobalPoint will always protect the personal information that you share with us. GlobalPoint stores information internally in a controlled, secure environment. If, for example, you make a purchase online, we route all transactions through SSL (Secure Socket Layers) and will process your credit card number only to secure your current payment.We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.If GlobalPoint requests general demographic information, this information is limited to reporting purposes only; users remain anonymous. Phone numbers, e-mail addresses, and postal addresses are not shared for demographic reports with outside entities.Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website.Storage of location data while using ExpensePoint MileageTracker™All location data that is collected when using the ExpensePoint mobile app is stored only on the user’s mobile device and ­not on the ExpensePoint servers. ExpensePoint will commit the storage of this data to its servers only when the user decides to expense the mileage based on the location data collected and stored on the users device, at which point the data is passed onto ExpensePoint at the express request of the user and an expense is created.Managing Your Data According to GDPRGlobalPoint Technologies is also GDPR compliant.  For more information on how GlobalPoint handles your data according to GDPR please click here.GlobalPoint & SecuritySecurity is one of our highest priorities, and GlobalPoint understands that security is important to our customers as well. GlobalPoint may use to publish security bulletins and technical briefs that provide information to customers about security issues.E-mailPostal Mail GlobalPoint Technologies Incorporated Attn: Privacy Dept. 104 Princess Street Winnipeg, Manitoba R3B 1K7 CanadaGlobalPoint would like to receive your comments and questions about this Privacy Policy:Please address comments or questions regarding the GlobalPoint Privacy Policy to one of the addresses listed above (online, e-mail, or postal mail). GlobalPoint may occasionally update, amend, or change this Privacy Policy based on user feedback and as needed or appropriate. If we decide to materially change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and will e-mail the information to our users so that they are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. Users will always have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in accordance with, and in respect to, the posted privacy policy.LinksGlobalPoint websites may contain links to other sites. GlobalPoint assumes no responsibility for the content or the privacy policies and practices of such websites. GlobalPoint encourages you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites; their privacy practices may differ from ours
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.I understandPrivacy policy
